K-pop!
That is so awkward to watch.
YouTube Rewind 2018.
The most disliked video
in the history of YouTube.
In 2018, we made something
you didn’t like.
So in 2019, let’s see what
you DID like.
Because you’re better at this
than we are.
This is my outfit!
What is it gonna be?
You made these the
MOST LIKED CREATOR VIDEOS
*of 2019, duh…
Shane Dawson | Conspiracy Theories with Shane Dawson
1.9M
A4 | ПОКУПАЮ ВСЁ ЧТО ТЫ МОЖЕШЬ УНЕСТИ ИЗ МАГАЗИНА !
2M
Andymation | My BIGGEST Flipbook EVER
2.3M
James Charles | No More Lies
2.4M
SethEverman | how to create billie eilish’s “bad guy”
2.8M
Nilson Izaias Papinho Oficial | Minha slime deu certo
Black Gryph0n | ONE GUY, 54 VOICES
3.4M
whinderssonnunes | O DIA EM QUE ASSISTI BIRD BOX
PewDiePie | Marzia &amp; Felix - Wedding
4.7M
MrBeast | Make This Video the Most Liked Video On YouTube
10.9M
The MOST LIKED
MUSIC VIDEOS
T-Series | Vaaste
5.5M
j-hope | Chicken Noodle Soup (feat. Becky G)
5.8M
Daddy Yankee &amp; Snow | Con Calma
7.5M
Lil Dicky | Earth
8.2M
Ariana Grande | 7 rings
9M
Lil Nas X | Old Town Road ft. Billy Ray Cyrus
9.6M
Billie Eilish | bad guy
10.3M
BLACKPINK | Kill This Love
10.8M
BTS | Boy With Luv feat. Halsey
12.8M
Shawn Mendes, Camila Cabello | Señorita
13.5M
the MOST LIKED
DANCE VIDEOS
Galen Hooks | Bury a Friend Choreography ft. Maddie Ziegler, Charlize Glass
525K
Team Naach | O SAKI SAKI Choreography
683K
1MILLION Dance Studio | gogobebe (고고베베) - MAMAMOO (마마무)
830K
Awez Darbar | O SAKI SAKI Choreography
897K
ChapkisDanceUSA | Con Calma Choreography
965K
the MOST VIEWED
VIDEO GAMES
Woah
Nice
Roblox
29.6B views
Garena Free Fire
29.9B views
Bien
Grand Theft Auto
36.9B views
Fortnite
60.9B views
Minecraft
100.2B views
Oh, wow.
the MOST LIKED
BEAUTY VIDEOS
Anaysa | 7 Life Saving HACKS for Perfect SKIN &amp; HAIR
540K
jeffreestar | Kylie Skin Review with Shane Dawson
1.1M
Just watch this.
Kylie Jenner | A Day in the Life
1.3M
Shane Dawson | The Beautiful World of Jeffree Star
1.4M
James Charles | Makeup Tutorial en Español
1.6M
Mucho, mucho.
Ah, no sé si quiero hacer mi sombra.
You helped these
NEW CREATORS
BREAK OUT
Shoaib Akhtar
Pakistan | First Upload: Feb 11, 2019
1.6M subscribers
LOUD Babi
Brazil | First Upload: April 10, 2019
1.7M subscribers
LOUD Coringa
Brazil | First Upload: Jan 29, 2019
1.8M subscribers
하루한끼 one meal a day
South Korea | First Upload: Jan 7, 2019
1.9M subscribers
Jennelle Eliana
USA | First Upload: June 26, 2019
2M subs
Noah Schnapp
USA | First Upload: June 11, 2019
2.1M subscribers
Magnet World
USA | First Upload: Jan 30, 2019
2.7M subscribers
백종원의 요리비책 Paik's Cuisine
South Korea | First Upload: June 10, 2019
2.9M subscribers
워크맨-Workman
South Korea | First Upload: August 16, 2019
3.2M subscribers
LOUD
Brazil | First Upload: Feb 28, 2019
3.4M subscribers
You made these the
MOST VIEWED CREATORS
Azzyland
1.9B views
Fischer's-フィッシャーズ-
LazarBeam
2B views
Let’s plant the trees!
MrBeast
2.2B views
Dude Perfect
2.3B views
David Dobrik
2.4B views
Jelly
2.5B views
I thought that was an avocado!
Pencilmation
2.8B views
Felipe Neto
PewDiePie
4B views
You
You LIKED
You DISLIKED
You WATCHED
You SUBSCRIBED
You COMMENTED
You SHARED
You UPLOADED
You PLAYED
You LISTENED
You SAVED
You CREATED
Thank you for a record breaking 2019
The first Thai creator
to hit 10 million subscribers
Became the largest
Spanish speaking channel
2019’s most watched
female artist in France
The first Middle Eastern creator
to hit 10 million subscribers
This education channel was
the first German creator
to pass 10 million subscribers
The first Indonesian creator
to hit 20 million subscribers
The first channel
to hit 100 million subscribers
The first European sports channel
to hit 10 million subscribers
Passed 1 billion views
with a single video
The first Turkish creator to hit
10 million subscribers
The biggest 24 hour debut
in YouTube history